(Raj:)He's right.
(Raj:)If you think about it,
we're all in charge.
(Sheldon:)No, the guy in charge is in...
(Sheldon:)Why is everyone so bad
at these?!
(Penny:)I mean, the whole experience
reminded me
(Penny:)about how much
I hated about that world.
You-you know, the anxiety,
the depression, the negativity.
(Penny:)I don't want
to feel those things.
(Penny:)I want to sell drugs to people
who feel those things.
(Amy:)I can't believe you got up
and walked out
(Amy:)of an audition for a big movie.
(Leonard:)I did.
I-I mean, I walked in,
read for the part,
(Penny:)then stunk up the place,
but then I walked right out.
(Bernadette:)Well, I'm glad
(Bernadette:)you have a new
appreciation for your job.
(Penny:)I do, and you know,
I don't think
(Penny:)I've ever thanked you properly
for helping me get it.
(Bernadette:)Properly, at all.
(Bernadette:)It's just words
I've never heard.
(Raj:)Well, thank you.
(Penny:)You're a good friend,
and you changed my life.
(Bernadette:)You're welcome.
(Bernadette:)Hey, now that
you're making some real money,
(Bernadette:)maybe you can take your friend
out for a nice thank-you dinner.
(Howard:)Sure.
(Amy:)And you probably have
to invite your other friend
(Amy:)'cause she overheard you
talking about it,
(Amy:)and it would be awkward
to exclude her.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Bernadette:)How about now?
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Bernadette:)Don't forget your wallet.
I... (groans)
(Sheldon(on screen):)Greetings from planet Earth.
(Sheldon(on screen):)Just turn left
at Alpha Centauri.
(Sheldon(on screen):)You can't miss it.